Ben: Hi. I’m back. Linda! What are you doing at home?
Linda: Hi, Dad. You’re very early.
Ben: Yes, I got an early flight.
Linda: Er, how was your day?
Ben: My day was fine. But what about your day? Why aren’t you at school?
Linda: We didn’t have classes today. We went to the British Museum in the morning.
It was great. And then we had lunch in the café there.
Ben: Why didn’t you go to school this afternoon?
Linda: We had a free afternoon. I stayed at home.
Ben: What did you do?
Linda: I did my homework. I had a lot of work.
Ben: Good girl. When are your exams?
Linda: They’re next week.
Ben: Where’s your mother?
Linda: She went out. I think she went shopping.
Ben: What’s that?
Linda: What?
Ben: That noise.